The End
North latitude 28 degrees 24 minutes,
west longitude 80 degrees 36 minutes.
Go there, and wait patiently
for the next new moon.
And that place is at Cape Canaveral
Space Center, to be precise.
The time is the new moon.
Six days from now.
Let's face the facts.
My old man would never
let that priest get away.
My name is Jolene Keicho.
It's up to me to seal what
that bastard just obtained.
It's a prison break, and we're
about to leave any minute.
Then I think you gotta take me with you.
So we're finally saying
adios to the aquarium, huh?
I thought this place was horrendous
when I first got locked up.
But now that I look back...
It's clear.
It really was a shithole.
So this is the gas station.
And this is the bus stop.
Are we going to be taking the bus here?
I've never actually been on one before.
You realize we're escaped convicts, right?
We'll get caught the second
we set foot on the bus yeah,
but if we're going after
the priest There's no way.
We'll be able to catch up to him on foot.
We know we just have to find another way
This is me guess mine
Let's go.
Thank you so
much for watching.
As you can't see,
I'm going to turn on the light of my life.
Or in her cell I can feel it in
the air she's finally free my guess
is she pulled off a prison break
hey
hang on a
birthmark shaped like a
star hmm who the hell are you I've
seen that star-shaped birthmark
somewhere before in the same place
on the back of the green baby's neck.
And supposedly, Jolene's
father bears a mark
that shares the same shape.
You'd better think hard
if you can't remember.
How exactly did you end
up at Green Dolphin?
Since you have no memory, does
that mean it's safe to assume
that the priest extracted your
memory disk like all the others?
He's my enemy.
That's all that I can tell you.
I need to learn the truth, so I'm
breaking out of here to find and end him.
What will you do?
This just in.
Two convicts have broken
out of Green Dolphin
Street State Prison and
are currently on the run.
The escaped convicts are Jolene
Cujo and Hermes Costello.
Photos of the two have been
released to the public.
Please contact us with any information.
Jolene,
it sounds as though you've defeated Mew
Mew Stand and you're intent on finding me.
Huh?
Why'd the car stop moving?
There's still plenty of gas in the tank.
Something like this has never happened.
I always take care of my vehicle.
I've got some bad news, Father.
This is as far as I can go.
My apologies.
Please let Let me call
another cab for you.
Thank you, but there is no need.
I'm not in any hurry.
I have a week until I'm born anew, and
I'm still in terrible physical condition.
Just five more days until the new moon.
Guess I can wait it out in this town.
I'll need to keep Jolene and
her friends away at all costs.
Hurry!
He's going into cardiac arrest!
This burglar was shot in
the leg by an officer,
then proceeded to jump off
the sixth floor of a building!
We've got a biker punk over here!
He drove against the floor of traffic
and slammed into the median strip!
What the hell's going on?
This drug addict is going into shock!
All right, listen up!
Stay back or the priest gets it!
Careful, the druggies
awake and out of control!
Damn it!
He cut me with those scissors!
Don't you point those fucking guns at me!
No way!
There ain't no way in hell
I'm gonna let you lock me up!
Requesting backup.
There's a hostage
situation at the hospital.
Hey, shit for brains!
What the hell did you just say?
Are you stupid, or do
you want this guy to die?
You really pissed me off now!
This fucking stone is about
to get stabbed because of you!
Earlier tonight, I saw shooting
stars in the sky above.
Three to be precise.
Just three, clearly
streaking across the sky.
May I ask where you came from?
Do you three have any idea
who it is you truly are?
Shit!
The psycho stabbed him!
Wait a sec, that wasn't me!
No, it wasn't.
However, if you were to move
this blade another millimeter,
it would certainly sever
a vital nerve in my neck.
What a coincidence.
Fortunately, this stab wound
does not appear to be fatal.
What will you do?
It's your decision.
Do you want to move the
scissors a bit or not?
But first, answer me this.
Do you believe in gravity?
Do you think there is a force that
draws certain individuals together?
Personally, this moment
has made me a believer.
However, you are not
capable of killing me.
You're here because my
gravitational pull led you to me.
Don't you see that you shouldn't be
wasting your energy on useless drugs?
No, you should be using your
energy on something much wiser.
Fuck this!
From the looks of things, where it
pertains to who your father really is,
The three of you were left in the dark,
but that won't last much longer.
Now that we've been brought together, you
will understand everything soon enough.
Thank you very much.
I'm fine.
Sorry to bother you.
This is nothing.
Just an old knee injury
from my carpentry days.
When it rains, my joints start to twinge.
When it rains, your knee hurts.
Sure does.
Thanks for showing me some kindness.
Stop getting into random
stranger's business, Weather.
We're still fugitives, remember?
Our faces are blasted all over the news.
The geezer might report us.
Our best bet is to steal a car and
get the hell out of Dodge immediately.
No stolen cars.
It'll be too easy for them to track us.
And then we'll never lose them.
Chasing the priest
would become impossible.
You're not suggesting we
take the bus, are you?
How long are we supposed to
wait till the next one comes?
Oh, hey, fellas.
You think I'm gonna take in the bus?
It won't be here for another hour.
How about I give you
boys a ride on my truck?
You'll have to hop in the back, though.
Maybe it's because you
were so kind to me earlier.
But I'm feeling better than ever.
The pain on my knees was awful moments
ago, but it's miraculously gone. Come on!
The sky feels so refreshing, too!
Weather forecast.
Call it luck.
We should take his offer, Anastasia.
So how's Jolene getting around right now?
She is still safe, isn't she?
Jolene is currently heading north.
Of that, I'm certain.
At any rate, we need to
be heading north as well.
There's a famous theme
park in the city up north.
You ever been there?
You wouldn't remember.
Remember, at this theme park, the
mascot's a really famous character.
Perhaps you might even know it.
This guidebook is a total piece of crap.
It doesn't even show any of
the famous characters in it.
Hey something's running around back here
could it be an enemy
dive or drive i got it
You sure i still see something darting
around yeah well i got this one for sure
But what the hell is this thing
Beyond the alert weather forecast
the stand user must be somewhere
There's zero chance this old man's
the stand user there's no reason
to show up the way he did He could
have just attacked us from anywhere.
If it's not him, it must be
someone else in the area.
Just like you're able to
sense where Jolene is going.
Maybe the priest can
sense us getting closer
and is sending his lackeys to
stop us from getting to him.
Now who the hell are you?
Tell us!
You really shouldn't do that.
Please stop choking me.
It hurts.
You're going to make children
all over the world very sad.
Is that so?
For real though, they can't breathe.
Come on, give it a rest.
Seriously, man, I'm begging you.
There's another little bastard
hiding on this truck, too.
Yeah, you two working together?
Uh, nuh-uh.
I work alone.
My bad, man.
So sorry about that.
I swear it wasn't on purpose.
You son of a...
Honestly, my nose just
grows on its own sometimes.
You know, it's sort of like a reflex.
See, whenever I tell a lie, my
nose gets all long and junk.
And I just lied straight to your face.
But what I told you wasn't exactly
a complete lie. So basically,
I might not be working with somebody,
but that doesn't mean that
I'm alone necessarily.
Yeah.
Oh!
Hey, check it out!
This proves I'm not lying.
You believe me now, right?
Ow! Shit! What are you?
Didn't I say to stop being so violent?
It feels kind of weird saying this about
myself, but I think I'm a pretty good guy.
I'm definitely nice to children, at least.
Actually, I might have been your
friend when you were younger.
Yeah, that's right.
Speaking of friends, I think the seven
of them are hiding around here somewhere.
I saw three of the seven
guys a minute ago. See?
Someone's been snacking
on that apple over there.
Hey, Weather, you seeing this?
What the fuck is going on?
Just so you know, that
apple isn't poisonous!
It's okay to eat.
Yeah, but the one Snow
White ate was poisonous.
No, she didn't actually eat it.
She choked on a piece of it.
So technically, she didn't digest it.
But I mean, who'd eat an apple
from an old lady they didn't know?
Even on Valentine's Day, we're careful
about the chocolates we put in our mouths.
Although it's that
carelessness of hers that
makes you want to protect
her with your whole life.
Holy shit, how many of you are there?
We've got some more company with her!
Chill, chill, there's nothing
to panic about here, buddy.
Who were you a fan of when you were a kid?
You know, who's your favorite character?
Maybe it was little old me?
Personally, I've got a thing
for the Terminator T-1000.
That guy ain't on the truck, though.
Me and my bro like Chewbacca.
And the Elephant Man, too.
But no matter what, our Princess Snow
White is the best character ever!
I do!
We know all the rumors about us?
Like how we like to sneak
into a girl's panties!
and do dirty things to
her, but they're lies.
Our relationship's
platonic all the way. Yeah!
These, these guys are,
they're so familiar.
I know them.
I mean, I know what they are,
but what the hell's going on?
We have breaking news.
Today at 1.30 PM, Batman suddenly
disappeared from all over the world.
I repeat, the beloved Batman is gone.
Paintings and prints of him
have also faded and we're
currently investigating the
cause of this phenomenon.
We've received several reports of other
famous characters vanishing as well.
You hear that, Weather?
Are these little freaks
who I think they are?
Does this mean they've
been brought to life?
But why?
What's the purpose?
Hey, who are you a fan of?
Do you like me?
I'm sorry, but I don't know who you are.
Now go away, or I'll kill you.
What the hell, Weather?
Did you really just take my stuff?
I was in the middle of
reading that, you know.
Give it back!
Where are you, Anastasia?
Hey, Anastasia, where'd you go?
Hey, old man, stop the truck!
What's wrong?
Weather, what is it?
I said pull over!
Oh, damn, that ain't good.
Yeah, it's bad. Good heavens! You guys!
Stop the damn truck rips!
Didn't you hear me say stop?
What is it?
What's going on, Weather?
Weather!
What the hell?
There's a body being dragged
underneath the truck, and it's mine!
What the fuck is going on?
Why is my body down there?
Looks like you've been separated, huh?
But anyway, you used to like
me a long time ago, right?
I knew you were a fan. No! Ah, shit.
At this rate, it'll get
caught in the tires.
Hey, Weather, make him stop the truck!
Wait, could he be?
Oh, goddammit!
We're gonna crash!
I made an airbag with weather forecast.
You all right?
How did you manage to fall
out of the truck so suddenly?
I'm pretty sure this is
a stand user's doing.
But I have no idea why you were
the only one who was targeted.
If I were to wager a guess,
I'd say it has something to do with
my ignorance of these characters.
That must be the reason.
Come on, Weather!
Did the wreck damage your eyes
or can you just not see me?
And is that my body
that's limp in your arms?
Everyone okay? Yeah!
But where's the princess?
Is she okay too?
She flew out of the truck and got
thrown towards that burger shop.
That's Hooper!
Hey, look!
Anybody know those guys?
I know them, but it ain't like
I'm friends with them or anything.
They're Japanese.
They've got some cool designs,
but they're totally overrated.
The characters from stories and
comics are brought into reality.
And in addition to that,
this stand has the ability to separate
someone's soul from their body.
That's the secret behind the stand, right?
Answer me, Pinocchio!
If you fantasy fucks or stands,
then where's the stand user?
I...
I don't know, buddy.
I honestly have no idea what's going on.
I mean, I'm just Pinocchio.
But why does something
like that even matter?
You could live your life as a
hero in the fantasy world, too.
The possibilities are endless.
Your soul split from your body because
that's what you truly wished would happen.
It's the realm where
everyone wishes to go.
Bohemian ecstatic.
Home of the Rhapsody of Freedom.
Just shut up.
If you refuse to answer my question,
I'll resort to more violence.
Wait, hold on a sec.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hey!
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Children all across this small
world of ours are on my side!
You bastard!
This is not how the
story's supposed to go!
Where'd weather go?
I can't afford to be separated
from him and my buddy.
Wait!
Please just wait!
Hey, old man.
You're the one who caused the accident
in the first place, so we're leaving.
Oh, hold on. Please wait.
I can't hear you very well.
Huh?
As you see, I have quite a lot of
hair growing on my ears these days.
Come closer, would you?
I don't have time for this.
Just sit tight and wait.
I'm sure someone will show up
soon and call you an ambulance.
Did you hurt your fingers, too?
Your nails are cracked.
That's not it.
I just have large hands.
All the better for hugging you
with is thanks for helping me
By the way, your pants are ripped
and something's coming out of there.
Oh,
this is just a feather
duster Your pants must
have gotten pretty dirty
when you saved my life.
How about you?
Let me dust them off for
you Hey, are you all right?
Your mouth is getting
freakishly big That's right!
All the better to devour you
with little red riding hood
DRIVE OR DRIVE!
This ending is just like this story.
Oh, what?
Did he just say story?
Weather!
I have a feeling that
Pinocchio, the dwarves,
and the other characters
aren't the actual stands.
The Stand user and their ability
exist elsewhere as separate entities,
and they brought these beings to life.
Towards the north,
somewhere not too far away.
That's the direction I sense
the enemy's ability coming from.
Pinocchio was just the beginning.
The Stand user must be taken down.
Weather!
Can't you hear what I'm saying?!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking
about Out all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer,
a distant dreamer,
dreaming for me.
From today
Thank you.
You